networkmarketing-local.com 2016-03-25

# 

                                      www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za
Privacy statement
www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za values the relationship we have with our customers and are committed to
responsible information handling practices.
Bertie van Greunen operate businesses and Web sites under the name Network Marketing Services. If you
provide information to any of the above businesses or Web sites, this information may be combined or shared
between current or future Network Marketing Services entities and subsidiaries.
Although our businesses, stores and Web sites have unique services and offerings, they share a similar privacy
philosophy. Network Marketing Services follows these privacy principles in our conduct in the collection, use,
release and security of customer information both online and offline:
         Giving you CHOICES about how your data will be used.
         Providing you NOTICE of our information practices.
         Providing you the opportunity to UPDATE or CORRECT your personal information.
         Using information SECURITY safeguards.
         Limiting the SHARING of your information.
         Committing to COMPLYING with applicable privacy requirements.
         Providing you with means to CONTACT US about privacy-related issues.
Network Marketing Services may modify its privacy policy as needed consistent with these principles.
www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za takes your privacy seriously, which is why we have created the following
policy for your protection and security. Please read it carefully.
What This Privacy Policy Covers
This Privacy Policy ("The Policy") covers www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za's treatment of personally
identifiable information that www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za collects when you are on the
www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za site, and when you use www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za's services.
The policy also covers www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za's treatment of any personally identifiable
information that www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za's business partners share with
www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za or that www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za may collect on a partner's
site.
This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za does not
own or control, or to people that www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za does not employ or manage.
Information Collection and Use
www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za collects personally identifiable information when you register for a a free
download - or free report, submit feedback or sign on as a member of the
www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za community.
When you register as a member of the www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za, we ask for your name,
occasionally a phone number and email address. Once you register with
www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za and sign in to our community, you are not anonymous to us.
www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za also automatically receives and records information on our server logs
from your browser including your IP Address, www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za cookie information, and the
page you requested.

www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za uses information for four general purposes: to customise the advertising
and content you see on our pages, to fulfil your requests for certain products and services, to contact you about
specials and new products and to send you the regular Wealth Insight Newsletter
Information Sharing and Disclosure
www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za and therefore Network Marketing Services community will not sell or rent
your personally identifiable information to anyone.
www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za and the Network Marketing Services community will only send personally
identifiable information about you to other companies or people when:
         We have your consent to share the information;
         We need to share your information in order to provide the product or service you have requested;
         We need to send the information to companies that work on behalf of
            www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za to provide a product or service to you. (Unless we tell you
            differently, these companies do not have any right to use the personally identifiable information we
            provide to them beyond what is necessary to assist us.);
         We respond to a compulsory court order to comply with due legal process; or
         We find that your actions on our web sites violate the www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za Rules - or
            any of our usage guidelines for specific products or services.
Cookies
www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za may set and access cookies on your computer. A cookie is a small
amount of data - which often includes an anonymous unique identifier - that is sent to your browser from a web
site's computer and stored on your computer's hard drive.
www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za allows other companies that are presenting advertisements on some of
our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. The way other companies use their cookies is
subject to their own privacy policies, not this one. Advertisers or other companies do not have access to
www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za’s cookies.
www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za uses web beacons to access our cookies within and outside our network
of web sites and in connection with www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za products and services. Web pages
may contain electronic images (called a "single-pixel GIF" or "web beacon") that allow a web site to count users
who have visited that page or to access certain cookies.
Your Ability to Edit and Delete Your Account Information and Preferences
You may change or update the information you have supplied www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za or the
Network Marketing Services community at any time. Please use the editing facilities available from your account
page to do this.
Security
Every effort is made to keep your information private and away from hackers. However, it is not possible for us to
guarantee your privacy. You should weigh up the risk that your details will be misused by hackers with the benefit
of receiving the great information that this site has to offer.

Who can I CONTACT if I have questions or concerns?
Please contact our Privacy Manager to report any known or suspected privacy or security breaches or to submit
privacy-related questions or complaints. After receiving your inquiry, we will respond within five business days.
You may contact us in the following ways:
Postal Mail:
Network Marketing Services
Attn: Privacy Manager
PO Box 1338
Worcester
6849
Email bertie@networkmarketingservices.co.za
Phone:+27 (0)82 557 5215
Will this Privacy Policy CHANGE?
Because our Web sites will continue to implement new technologies and improve the services and features we
provide, this policy is subject to change. If there are changes or additions to this Privacy Policy, we will post those
changes here or in other formats we deem acceptable, so that you will always know what information we collect
online or offline, how we use it and what choices you have. If we change our information practices or this Privacy
Policy in such a way that your personal information may be used or shared in a different manner, we will give you
the choice to opt-out of having your past information used or shared in that new manner.
Last revision date: June 07, 2015
www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za has reviewed and rewritten its Privacy Policy to (1) make it easier to read
and understand, (2) describe its practices in better detail, (3) make it clear that we may combine or share the
information we hold across all current or future the Network Marketing Services community, and (4) combine
privacy policies and practices for the Network Marketing Services retail stores and its affiliates. Instead of having
multiple and potentially conflicting privacy policies for the Network Marketing Services entities and our Web sites,
we have decided to ensure all the Network Marketing Services entities operations follow the same privacy
standards. By combining our privacy policies and practices, we give our customers the same privacy standards
whether providing the Network Marketing Services personal information on or offline. If you have questions about
our Privacy Policy, email our Privacy Manager at bertie@networkmarketingservices.co.za
www.NetworkMarketingServices.co.za may edit this policy from time to time. If we make any substantial changes
we will notify you by posting a prominent announcement on our pages.
                         Copyright © 2015 Network Marketing Services | All Rights Reserved
                                                       Contact Us
    Disclaimer (According to FTC guidelines) you will need to be informed that sometimes Network Marketing
Services will get paid for recommending certain products on this website. Not all the time, but often. The Terms of
                                   Use includes further information of this disclaimer.
